Atmospheric Sciences and Research Center; Records ua450
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Department Website, 2014 October 17 - 2017 May 17; 1; 96 captures
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 July 17
    crawl: 225859
    start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-22T22:52:35Z
    end_date: 2016-07-22T17:55:28Z
    elapsed_ms: 435383503
    discovered_count: 6792375
    novel_count: 212820
    duplicate_count: 1098346
    queued_count: 5481209
    downloaded_count: 1311166
    download_failures: 256
    warc_revisit_count: 1098317
    warc_url_count: 1311042
    total_data_in_kbs: 212249210
    duplicate_bytes: 207609316437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 675349961
    doc_rate: 3.01
    kb_rate: 487.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 July 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 August 17
    crawl: 231044
    Block host dev.library.albany.edu
    start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-23T01:20:50Z
    end_date: 2016-08-22T23:33:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 455703830
    discovered_count: 1189467
    novel_count: 184079
    duplicate_count: 736427
    queued_count: 268961
    downloaded_count: 920506
    download_failures: 267
    warc_revisit_count: 736404
    warc_url_count: 920384
    total_data_in_kbs: 202254345
    duplicate_bytes: 198029314926
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397770039
    doc_rate: 2.02
    kb_rate: 443.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 August 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 September 23
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 October 18
    crawl: 243096
    start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-22T20:32:46Z
    end_date: 2016-10-22T17:07:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 432270469
    discovered_count: 1819420
    novel_count: 557303
    duplicate_count: 900445
    queued_count: 361672
    downloaded_count: 1457748
    download_failures: 296
    warc_revisit_count: 900407
    warc_url_count: 1457649
    total_data_in_kbs: 215568357
    duplicate_bytes: 201221539907
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1485925187
    doc_rate: 3.37
    kb_rate: 498.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 October 18
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 November 17
    crawl: 249672
    start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-22T23:26:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-22T18:15:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 436686458
    discovered_count: 6455397
    novel_count: 904107
    duplicate_count: 647491
    queued_count: 4903799
    downloaded_count: 1551598
    download_failures: 287
    warc_revisit_count: 647445
    warc_url_count: 1551482
    total_data_in_kbs: 234676600
    duplicate_bytes: 166348006398
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22645478722
    doc_rate: 3.55
    kb_rate: 537.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 November 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 December 18
    crawl: 255339
    start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-22T23:02:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-22T17:39:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 434651176
    discovered_count: 5605147
    novel_count: 672626
    duplicate_count: 721586
    queued_count: 4210935
    downloaded_count: 1394212
    warc_revisit_count: 721559
    warc_url_count: 1394095
    total_data_in_kbs: 173161585
    duplicate_bytes: 152072050167
    warc_compressed_bytes: 4226018506
    doc_rate: 3.21
    kb_rate: 398.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2016 December 18
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 January 17
    crawl: 261028
    start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-23T00:48:05Z
    end_date: 2017-01-22T19:31:33Z
    elapsed_ms: 440845477
    discovered_count: 6856243
    novel_count: 810250
    duplicate_count: 844972
    queued_count: 5201021
    downloaded_count: 1655222
    download_failures: 351
    warc_revisit_count: 844920
    warc_url_count: 1655090
    total_data_in_kbs: 260833049
    duplicate_bytes: 210669517964
    warc_compressed_bytes: 15598206209
    doc_rate: 3.75
    kb_rate: 591.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 January 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 February 17
    crawl: 267806
    start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T23:52:19Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T17:57:15Z
    elapsed_ms: 435595208
    discovered_count: 6181071
    novel_count: 757736
    duplicate_count: 820126
    queued_count: 4603209
    downloaded_count: 1577862
    download_failures: 339
    warc_revisit_count: 820090
    warc_url_count: 1577729
    total_data_in_kbs: 257873727
    duplicate_bytes: 232995142726
    warc_compressed_bytes: 5661819855
    doc_rate: 3.62
    kb_rate: 592.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 February 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 March 17
    crawl: 273971
    start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 436406787
    discovered_count: 7409222
    novel_count: 690900
    duplicate_count: 1257496
    queued_count: 5460826
    downloaded_count: 1948396
    download_failures: 359
    warc_revisit_count: 1257455
    warc_url_count: 1948270
    total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
    duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
    doc_rate: 4.46
    kb_rate: 611.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 March 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 April 17
    crawl: 291352
    start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-22T22:22:12Z
    end_date: 2017-04-22T17:55:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 435220728
    discovered_count: 8221578
    novel_count: 736180
    duplicate_count: 1311488
    queued_count: 6173910
    downloaded_count: 2047668
    download_failures: 335
    warc_revisit_count: 1311435
    warc_url_count: 2047538
    total_data_in_kbs: 284745035
    duplicate_bytes: 261915565851
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2411311996
    doc_rate: 4.7
    kb_rate: 654.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 April 17
  - Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 May 17
    crawl: 301465
    Host Rule Type C CONTAINS meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search? (last updated 2017-05-11)
    start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-23T00:29:43Z
    end_date: 2017-05-22T21:46:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 449440076
    discovered_count: 2923335
    novel_count: 388249
    duplicate_count: 1238165
    queued_count: 1296921
    downloaded_count: 1626414
    download_failures: 336
    warc_revisit_count: 1238113
    warc_url_count: 1626286
    total_data_in_kbs: 265327774
    duplicate_bytes: 251274786133
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3306915146
    kb_rate: 590.0
  - WARC file for Department of Atmospheric and Environmental Sciences - College of Arts and Sciences - University at Albany - SUNY, 2017 May 17
- Subject Files, 1961-1999; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - "Albany" Magazine- University at Albany Magazine, 1999 Spring (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Adirondak Conference or Silver Iodide Phenomena, 1992 November (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - ASRC at Yellowstone- State University Newsletter, 1966 February (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - ASRC Correspndence, 1961; 1965-1969; 1971; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - ASRC General Program, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - ASRC Press Release, 1964 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - ASRC Publication lists, 1971; 1972 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - ASRC Whiteface Mountain Science Lectures, 1973; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Reference List For General Information Reading, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center Facility Proposal, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - "The Basic Philosophy + Objectives of the ASRC" by Dr. Vincent J. Schaeler, 1967 October 6 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - "A Change in the Weather" by Austin W. Hogem & Raymond E. Falocner, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence of Dr. Katherine H. Heining, 1964; 1965 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Dependence of Freezing Temperature of Supercold Water Drops on Rate of Cooling by Narayan Gokhale, 1964 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Ecology Lecture: Acid Rain: Causes & Consequences by Gene E. Likens, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Energy Education Project, 1983; 1984; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Environment Conservation Institute, 1973-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Establishment of an Instiute for Atmospheric Science, 1960 November 3 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Exploratory In-Flight Survey of the Continental United State, 1966 December 1 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - The Fog Project- Report, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - The Gas- Heating Phase in Electrical Breakdown by Ernesto Barreto, 1983 October (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Global Survey of Atmosphere Aerosol, NSF Project Report, 1978 December 29 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Grants Submitted & Under Review, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - "Great Lakes Snowstorms" Grant, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Informational Research Report- Small Utility Internal Combustion Engine Test, 1972 March 15 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Lake George Institute, 1972; 1974; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Memorandum of Proposed Northeastern New York Chapter of the American Section of the International Solar Energy Society, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - The Mirco-World in the Atmosphere, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Natural History Lecture Series, 1973-1977; 1984-1985; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Natural History Institute, 1966; 1967; 1974 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - New York Engery Education Project, 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Ninth International Conference on Atmospheric Aerosols Condensation & Ice Nuclei, 1977 September (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Performance Evaluation of the National Lightning Detection Network in the Vincinity of Albany, New York- Final Report, 1997 December (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - "Political Boundaries & Pollution Control" by Joseph F. Zimmermen, 1967 August 15 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Project "Air Sample IV", 1968 November 8-27; 1968 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Proposal "Economic & Technical Feasibility of Lawand Solar-Heated Greenhouse In Northern Regions, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - A Proposal for the Establishment of an Atmospheric Science Research Center, 1961 February 3 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Second Annual Revision of the First Three-Year-Plan, 1977-1980 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - A Selected Bibliography of Solar Information, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Snowflakes- How to Identify & Perserve Them, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Solar Energy Education, 1979; 1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Solar Energy Education- Renewable Energy Activities for Biology, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Solar Energy Education- Renewable Energy Activities for Chemistry + Physics, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Solar Energy Education- Renewable Energy Activities for Earth Science, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Solar Energy Education- Renewable Energy Activities for General Science, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Solar Energy Education- Renewable Energy Activities for Junior High/Middle School Science, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - "Solar Energy for New York State" Position Paper by Volker A. Mohnen, 1975 May 20 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Solar Demonstration Project-NYSERDA, 1979 November (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - "Solar Supplements for Heating & Air Conditioning" by Charles F. Harrington, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - SUNY-Albany Lightning Detection Network-Thunder--Data Access Software, 1987 January (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - SUNY-Albany University-Wide Conference on Atmospheric Sciences, 1967 October (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Three Stages of Fragmentation of Hydrometeors, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Three Year Plan by Volker A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - "Variations in Aitken & Giant Nuclei in Marine Air" by Duncan C. Blanchard & Lawrence Syzdek, 1972 January 28 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Weather Modification Conference, 1968; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Whiteface Mountain Field Station, 1961; 1963; 1976-1978; 1983-1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Whiteface Mountain Field Station, 1961; 1963; 1976-1978; 1983-1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Wintertime Trace Gas + Cloudwater Chemistry Studies-Whiteface Mountain-J.A. Kadlecek, 1988 January (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 60)
- Publications, 1961-1992; 3; 5.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged Chronologically.
  - Final Report 1961 Yellowstone Field Research Seminar (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Hailstorms & Hailstones of the Western Great Plains, 1961 December 18 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Forest Ecology of Ice Storms, 1961 January (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Final Report Yellowstone Field Research Seminar, 1962 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Report of Proceedings NCAR-ASRC-SUNY Adirondack Conference on Silver Iodide Phenomina, 1963 March 20 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Adirondack Conference on Silver Iodide Phenomona, 1963 July (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Amateur Scientist, 1962 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Vapor Method & Making Replicas of liquid & Soild Aerosols, 1962 September (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Some Problems Concerning Weather Control, 1962 September (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Condensed Water in the Free Atmosphere in Air Colder than -40C, 1962 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Electric-Field Perturbations by Eruption of Yellowstone Geysers, 1963 March (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
  - A Pilot Project in the Atomspheric Sciences for Young Stundents (Spring), 1963 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Interim-Report Third Yellowstone field Research Expedition, 1963 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Observations & Experiments for Cooperative Studies of "Lake Effect" Snowstorms, 1962 May (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Report of Whiteface Mountain Activities of the Atmospheric Sciences Research Center, 1963 June 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Programs for High Ability Students, 1961 October (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Studies of Atmospheric Nuclei in Yellowstone Park, 1963 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Amateur Scientist: How to make & Investigate vortexs on Water & Flame, 1963 October (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Interim Report of the Natural Sciences Institute, 1963 November 11 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Final Report Natural Sciences Institute, 1963 September 15 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 19A)
  - Procedings of the Confrence on Lake-Effect Storms, 1962 April 23/24 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Whiteface Mountain Summer Program, 1963 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Whiteface Mountain Summer Program, 1964 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 21-A)
  - Final Report-Fourth Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1964 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Second Interim Report of the Natural Sciences Institute, 1964 September 20 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Final Report-Research Support of 1964 Flagstaff Field Operations, 1964 September 20 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 23-A)
  - Condensation Nuclei Counts on the Slopes of Little Whiteface Mountain in New York State, 1963 November 21 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Small Ion Concentrations in and near Clouds & Fogs, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 25)
  - A Simple Method for Obtaining a Continuous Record of the Presence&Type of Clouds in the Sky During the Day, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 26)
  - A Color Code File System For Easy Retrieval of Correlated Atmospheric Events, 1964 April (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 27)
  - A Suggested Origin of Conical Graupel, 1964 October (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Preparation of Permenant Replicas of Snow, Frost, and Ice, 1964 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Studies of Weather Phenomena to the Lee of the Eastern Great Lakes, 1964 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Interim Report-Fifth Yellowstone Field Research Expedtion, 1965 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Final Report of the Natural Sciences Institute for the Years, 1965 September 10 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 32)
  - ASRC Research Reports, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 33)
  - The Detection of Silver Iodide in Snow by Neutron Activation Analysis, 1965 April/June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 34)
  - The Amateur Scientist- On Preserving the Shapes of snow crystals by catching snowflakes in dissolved plastic, 1966 March (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Weather Modification, 1967 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Interim Report -Sixth Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1966 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 37)
  - Sixth International Confernce on Condensation Nuclei, 1966 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 38-A)
  - Lightning Strikes A Parked School Bus, 1966 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Final Report-Research Support of 1966 Flagstaff Field Operations, 1966 August 28 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 40-A)
  - Final Report of the Natural Sciences Institute, 1966 September 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Snowflakes-Identification & Preservation, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Langmuir Circulations and Internal Waves in Lake George, 1966 November (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 42)
  - A Preliminary Study of Water Motions in Lake George & Lake Champlain, 1966 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 43)
  - The Blizzard of '66 in Central New York State-Lengend in its Time, 1966 December (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 44)
  - Final Report-Seventh Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1967 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 45)
  - Dynamic Behavior of Nuclei in Ice Formation, 1966 June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 46)
  - Air Mass Modification by Lake Ontario During the April-November Period, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 47)
  - Prevailing Winds on Whiteface Mountain as Indicated by Flag Trees, 1970 June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 48)
  - Ice Nuclei from Automobile Exhaust & Iodine Vapor, 1966 December 23 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 49)
  - Some Characteristics of Aitken Nuclei Concentrations, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 50)
  - The Detection of Surface Active Molecules on Airborne Particles, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 51)
  - Dic Wirkungsweise des akustischen Teilchenzahlers, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 52)
  - Discussion of Paper by J. Brain Matthews, Mass Loss & Distortion of Free Falling Water Drops in an Electric Field- B. Vonnegat, 1968 February (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 53)
  - Windgeschwindigkeiten in Tornados- B. Vonnegat, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 54)
  - Fifth Report of the Natural Sciences Institute, 1967 September 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 55)
  - Anlagerungsvorgange Radioktiver Aerosole- Volker Mohnen, 1968 February 29 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 56)
  - Windchill- Compiled by Raymond Falconer, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 57)
  - Ice Nuclei from Auto Exhaust & Organic Vapors- V.J. Schaefer, 1968 February (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 58)
  - Aitken Nuclei Obeservations over the North Atlantic Ocean -by A.W. Hogan, J.M. Bishop, A.L. Aymer, B.W. Harlow, J.C. Klepper & G. Lupo, 1967 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 59)
  - The Role of Langmuir Circulation in Mixing of Lake George- Jon T. Scott & Ronald Stewart, 1968 August (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 60)
  - Gradient Circulation in Eastern Lake Ontario- Jon T. Scott & Livingston Lansing, 1967 November (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 61)
  - Ice Nuclei from Direct Reaction of Iodine Vapor with Vapors from Leaded Gasoine- Austin W. Hogan, 1967 November 10 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 62)
  - The Early History of Weather Modification - V.J. Schaefer, 1968 April (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 63)
  - Krypton Diffusion in Scintillation Conter Plastic- Francis J. Norton, 1968 April 13 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 67)
  - Interim Report Eighth Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1968 May 1 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 68)
  - Something in the Air - V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 69)
  - The Effect of the Nucleus on Ice Crystal Structure -V.J. Schaefer & J.L. Cheng, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 70)
  - The Generation of Large Numbers of Ice Crystals in an Electric Field- V.J. Schaefer, 1968 June (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 71)
  - The effects of a Trace of Iodine on Ice Nucleation Measurements, 1968 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 74)
  - A Portable Nucleus Counte of Increased Sensitivity - A.W. Hogan & G. Gardener, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 75)